(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{12:function(t,e,s){t.exports=s(19)},17:function(t,e,s){},18:function(t,e,s){},19:function(t,e,s){"use strict";s.r(e);var n=s(0),r=s.n(n),o=s(6),a=s.n(o),i=(s(17),s(7)),c=s(8),u=s(2),l=s(11),h=s(10),d=function(t){var e=t.gameOver;return r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"text-center mb-5"},!1===e?"Quiz App":"Game over")},m=function(t){var e=t.value;return r.a.createElement("h4",{className:"mb-4"},e)},p=function(t){var e=t.index,s=t.text,n=t.checkAnswer,o=t.correctAnswerIndex,a=t.showIndicator,i=t.disabledBtns;return r.a.createElement("button",{className:"answerBtn form-control mb-2 \n                ".concat(!0===a&&o===e?"correct":"","\n                ").concat(!0===i?"disabled":""),type:"button",onClick:function(){return n(e)}},s)},b=function(t){var e=t.options,s=t.checkAnswer,n=t.correctAnswerIndex,o=t.showIndicator,a=t.disabledBtns;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group"},e.map((function(t,e){return r.a.createElement(p,{key:e,index:e,text:t,correctAnswerIndex:n,showIndicator:o,checkAnswer:s,disabledBtns:a})})))},f=s(9),w=(s(18),s(21)),v=function(t){var e=t.score,s=t.restart;return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h4",null,"Your score: ",e),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary w-75 d-block mx-auto my-4",onClick:function(){return s()}},"Play again!"))},g=function(t){Object(l.a)(s,t);var e=Object(h.a)(s);function s(t){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,s),(n=e.call(this,t)).state={qaList:f,question:"",options:[],correctAnswer:"",showIndicator:!1,isCorrect:null,score:0,round:0,progress:0,disabledBtns:!1},n.checkAnswer=n.checkAnswer.bind(Object(u.a)(n)),n.restart=n.restart.bind(Object(u.a)(n)),n}return Object(c.a)(s,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.shuffleArray(this.state.qaList),this.getQuestion(),console.log(this.state.qaList)}},{key:"checkAnswer",value:function(t){var e=this;this.setState({round:this.state.round+1,disabledBtns:!0},(function(){e.setState({progress:Math.ceil(e.state.round/e.state.qaList.length*100)}),t===e.state.correctAnswerIndex&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({isCorrect:t===e.state.correctAnswerIndex,showIndicator:!0}),e.state.round<e.state.qaList.length&&e.nextQuestion()}))}},{key:"nextQuestion",value:function(){var t=this;setTimeout((function(){t.getQuestion(),t.setState({isCorrect:null,showIndicator:!1,disabledBtns:!1}),document.activeElement.blur()}),1500)}},{key:"getQuestion",value:function(){this.setState({question:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].question,options:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].opt,correctAnswerIndex:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].correct})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(t){for(var e=t.length-1;e>0;e--){var s=Math.floor(Math.random()*(e+1)),n=[t[s],t[e]];t[e]=n[0],t[s]=n[1]}return t}},{key:"restart",value:function(){this.setState({showIndicator:!1,isCorrect:null,score:0,round:0,progress:0,disabledBtns:!1})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},r.a.createElement(d,{gameOver:this.state.round===this.state.qaList.length}),this.state.round===this.state.qaList.length?r.a.createElement(v,{score:this.state.score,restart:this.restart}):r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(m,{value:this.state.question}),r.a.createElement(b,{options:this.state.options,correctAnswerIndex:this.state.correctAnswerIndex,checkAnswer:this.checkAnswer,showIndicator:this.state.showIndicator,disabledBtns:this.state.disabledBtns}),r.a.createElement(w.a,{now:this.state.progress,label:"".concat(this.state.progress,"%"),variant:100==this.state.progress?"success":""})))}}]),s}(r.a.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(g,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(t){t.unregister()})).catch((function(t){console.error(t.message)}))},9:function(t){t.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"What is the largest mammal?","opt":["Dog","Cat","Horse","All the same"],"correct":3},{"question":"How does one gain the ability to fly?","opt":["You fly","Become birb","Not possible","Just do it"],"correct":1},{"question":"If I can fly in my dreams, am I a birb?","opt":["Yes","No","Maybe","Perhaps"],"correct":0},{"question":"How many dogs exist?","opt":["5","10","666","5 594 338 000"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is 5+5?","opt":["5","No","10","Not a number"],"correct":2},{"question":"How many cats are needed?","opt":["75756","429347573275","5","None"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is love?","opt":["Baby don\'t hurt me","Don\'t hurt me","No more","An illusion ;_;"],"correct":3},{"question":"What is the radius of you\'re house? (in meters)","opt":["5","285","420","10000"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is the mass of the Sun? (in tonnes)","opt":["A lot","500","5","The Sun has no mass"],"correct":1},{"question":"How fast does light travel?","opt":["5","Yes","Fast","At the speed of light"],"correct":3},{"question":"What are birbs actually?","opt":["Surveillance drones","Horses","Birbs","Borbs"],"correct":0},{"question":"How is it possible to get a horse?","opt":["It\'s not possible","Horses are not real","Just get it","Bribe the government"],"correct":3}]')}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.30dcacb7.chunk.js.map